http://www.neffpower.com/about/privacy-policy

Toll Free:
Who We Are
We have a Mobile App!
Privacy Policy / Terms & Conditions
What information do we collect?We collect information from you when you fill out a form. When contacting us through our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, company affiliation, mailing address, or phone number.This website uses Hotjar web analytics service. Hotjar may record mouse clicks, mouse movements and scrolling activity. Hotjar collects information regarding pages visited, actions which are taken, country, device used, operating system, and browser used. Hotjar does not collect personally identifiable information (PII) that you do not voluntarily enter in this website. Hotjar does not track your browsing habits across web sites which do not use Hotjar services. What do we use your information for?Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)To send periodic emails. The email address you provide may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your inquiry, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.To improve our website and services, to make it more user-friendly, and to monitor that it is performing correctly. How do we protect your information?We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.Email confidentiality:This transmission and any attached files are confidential or otherwise the exclusive property of the intended recipient or Neff Power Inc. If you are not the intended recipient, any disclosure, copying, distribution or use of any of the information contained in or attached to this transmission is prohibited. If you have received this transmission in error, please contact us immediately by e-mail (administrator@neffpower.com) and promptly destroy the original transmission and its attachments. Opinions, conclusions and other information in this message that do not relate to the official business of Neff Power shall be understood as neither given nor endorsed by Neff Power.
Do we use cookies?Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.We use cookies to compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business. Use of re-marketing with Google Analytics and/or Google AdwordsWe collect cookies on our Web site to capture information about page visits. This information is anonymous and we use this information only internally - to deliver the most effective content to our visitors. Information from the cookies is used to gauge page popularity, analyze traffic patterns on our site and guide development of other improvements to our site. We do not require that you accept cookies; however, some functionality on our Web site, our product or service check-out process, and products and services may be disabled if you decline to accept cookies. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it. You may also change your cookie settings through preferences options in our products and/or services, where applicable. We never give away information about our users. If you choose to e-mail us and provide personally identifiable information about yourself, we will use this information only to respond to your inquiry. We will not sell, rent or otherwise disclose that information to third parties unless such disclosure is necessary for the purposes set forth in this Policy, by law or a policy or notice contained or associated with a specific product or service.We use analytics data and the DoubleClick cookie to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to our website. This enables us to match the right site visitors with the right advertising message. Site visitors may opt out of the DoubleClick cookie by visiting the Google advertising opt-out page or they may opt out of Google Analytics by visiting the Google Analytics opt-out pageYou can also opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out pageYou may also use the following cookie opt-outsGoogle Advertising Cookie Opt-Out PluginGoogle Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-onDo we disclose any information to outside parties?We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses. Third party linksOccasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third-party products or services on our website. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We, therefore, have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites. Children's online privacy protection act complianceWe are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children's Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, our products, and our services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older. Online privacy policy onlyThis online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline. Your consentBy using our site, you consent to our online privacy policy.Changes to our privacy policyIf we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.
For over 50 years, Neff Power has established trust with our customers by providing quality products and services.
Neff Power is an ISO 9001:2015 certified company and we are constantly focused on improving our service to our customers.
675 Spirit Valley Central Dr.
